Okay, because people want more clarity on this. So yes, registering has already been a part of the
American expectation. However, now this is saying that you will automatically be registered.
The Senate still has to pass this. There is bipartisan support. They also have added women
to this. And the biggest element of this that I want y'all to pay attention to is the fact that
whenever you start to see a government tinker with things that have already been precedent
or that have already been passed, it's because they want to do something more extreme. They tinker
first to see what the temperature is, to see if they can get anything shaken, and then they will
then move on. And they do things like this also to check what the populace is going to say. So when
I see so many people respond to this tinkering right here with, oh, it's going to free up funds
and they'll reallocate the funds. That means that they understand that so many of the populace
still thinks that this government is working for them. Reallocate funds for what? You think
they're going to reallocate funds for healthcare? You think they're going to reallocate funds for
the houseless population? You think they're going to reallocate funds for reparations? Yeah,
no dice. Those reallocated funds are going to war. Much of the reason American news doesn't talk
about anywhere else is because they don't want you paying attention to anywhere else. But ultimately,
America is an imperialist empire that is actively harming the world and it will come back on us.
It's inevitable.